[{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980304300,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":24110,"timeElapsed":106978},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980319262,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":14960,"timeElapsed":121940},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980326329,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":7066,"timeElapsed":129007},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980337392,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":11061,"timeElapsed":140070},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980340642,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":3249,"timeElapsed":143320},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980350423,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":9780,"timeElapsed":153101},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980354410,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3986,"timeElapsed":157088},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980363582,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":9170,"timeElapsed":166260},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980372378,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":8795,"timeElapsed":175056},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980383776,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":9375,"timeElapsed":186454},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980386110,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2332,"timeElapsed":188787},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980389974,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":3864,"timeElapsed":192652},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980394322,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":4347,"timeElapsed":197000},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980400571,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":6248,"timeElapsed":203249},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980407959,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":7386,"timeElapsed":210637},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980413749,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":5789,"timeElapsed":216427},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980438062,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":24312,"timeElapsed":240740},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980446822,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":8758,"timeElapsed":249500},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980456751,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":9089,"timeElapsed":259429},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980459959,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3206,"timeElapsed":262637},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980463215,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":3255,"timeElapsed":265893},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980466106,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2890,"timeElapsed":268784},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980469539,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3432,"timeElapsed":272217},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980477397,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":7857,"timeElapsed":280075},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980491606,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":14208,"timeElapsed":294284},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980496310,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4703,"timeElapsed":298988},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980501231,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":4920,"timeElapsed":303909},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980508690,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":6626,"timeElapsed":311368},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980511815,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":3124,"timeElapsed":314493},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980515097,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":3281,"timeElapsed":317775},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980517453,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":2354,"timeElapsed":320131},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980519328,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":1875,"timeElapsed":322006},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980525635,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":6306,"timeElapsed":328313},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980528768,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":3132,"timeElapsed":331446},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980538709,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":9940,"timeElapsed":341387},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980542305,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3595,"timeElapsed":344983},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980552489,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":9095,"timeElapsed":355167},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980554650,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2160,"timeElapsed":357328},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980558207,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":3556,"timeElapsed":360885},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980560985,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":2777,"timeElapsed":363663},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980565344,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":4359,"timeElapsed":368022},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980571417,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":6072,"timeElapsed":374095},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980573618,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":2200,"timeElapsed":376296},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980578785,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":5166,"timeElapsed":381463},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980580066,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":1280,"timeElapsed":382744},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980618124,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":37075,"timeElapsed":420802},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980620687,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2562,"timeElapsed":423365},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980623499,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2811,"timeElapsed":426177},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980625190,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":1690,"timeElapsed":427868},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980627446,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":2256,"timeElapsed":430124},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980631955,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":4508,"timeElapsed":434633},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980634077,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2121,"timeElapsed":436755},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980637964,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3886,"timeElapsed":440642},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980640225,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2260,"timeElapsed":442903},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980648294,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":7020,"timeElapsed":450972},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980650499,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":2204,"timeElapsed":453177},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980653573,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":3073,"timeElapsed":456251},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980655720,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":2146,"timeElapsed":458398},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980657372,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":1650,"timeElapsed":460050},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980665391,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":8019,"timeElapsed":468069},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980668591,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":3199,"timeElapsed":471269},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980671503,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":2910,"timeElapsed":474180},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980680669,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":9166,"timeElapsed":483347},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980683820,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":3150,"timeElapsed":486498},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980692980,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":8233,"timeElapsed":495658},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980697827,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":4845,"timeElapsed":500505},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980701185,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":3357,"timeElapsed":503863},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980702984,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":1798,"timeElapsed":505662},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980705698,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":2713,"timeElapsed":508376},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980709569,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":3870,"timeElapsed":512247},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980712189,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":2619,"timeElapsed":514867},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980716015,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":3824,"timeElapsed":518692},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980719456,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":3440,"timeElapsed":522133},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980732478,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":11997,"timeElapsed":535156},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980734499,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":2020,"timeElapsed":537177},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980754365,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":19865,"timeElapsed":557043},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980756345,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":1978,"timeElapsed":559023},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980757917,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":1571,"timeElapsed":560595},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980763200,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":5282,"timeElapsed":565878},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980765665,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":2464,"timeElapsed":568343},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980770468,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4802,"timeElapsed":573146},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980774041,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":3572,"timeElapsed":576719},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980776285,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":2243,"timeElapsed":578963},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980785189,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":7861,"timeElapsed":587867},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980787708,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2518,"timeElapsed":590386},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980790406,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2697,"timeElapsed":593084},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980794895,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4487,"timeElapsed":597573},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980796316,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":1420,"timeElapsed":598994},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980800406,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":4089,"timeElapsed":603084},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980803591,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":3184,"timeElapsed":606269},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980805964,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2372,"timeElapsed":608642},{"subjectID":"yshy6uxasg","prolificID":"55d234b45bc5bc0005d9039d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24dd8f908f26f914f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980809528,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3563,"timeElapsed":612206}]